<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GuideApp</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="monument_names">
        <item>Mausoleum of Asaf ibn Burkhiy</item>
        <item>Arch Kyrgyz nomad</item>
        <item>Lenin Statue</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hyperlinks_monuments">
        <item>&lt;a href="https://goo.gl/maps/8khMjuDBkBbdHtqb7">Oш&lt;/a></item>
        <item>&lt;a href="https://goo.gl/maps/dsKitay1QMk2yg1y8">ул. Памирская, Ош&lt;/a></item>
        <item>&lt;a href="https://goo.gl/maps/z8UQQ2KLbpLAdTei6">Городская площадь, Ош&lt;/a></item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc">
        <item>The mausoleum of Asaf ibn Burhiya is located in the historical center of Osh, not far from the Sulaiman-Too museum complex, located at the mountain of the same name. The Historical Museum, Art Gallery named after Gapar Aitiev, Museum of Arts, Osh State University and Alisher Navoi Park are also located in the immediate vicinity of the mausoleum.\n
According to legend, an associate of King Sulaiman Asaf ibn Burhiya is buried here, who bequeathed to bury him at the foot of the mountain. Built in the 18th century, the mausoleum has been destroyed and rebuilt more than once over its long history. Currently, the building is The mausoleum of Asaf ibn Burhiya is located in the historical center of Osh, not far from the Sulaiman-Too museum complex, located at the mountain of the same name. The Historical Museum, Art Gallery named after Gapar Aitiev, Museum of Arts, Osh State University and Alisher Navoi Park are also located in the immediate vicinity of the mausoleum.\n
The building of the mausoleum is a classic example of such a structure, erected in the style of the architecture of the ancient mausoleums of Bukhara and Samarkand. The main room of the mausoleum is decorated with a massive entrance portal, in the upper part of which there are four decorative windows, which are closed with ornamental lattices. The interior of the entrance arch is tiledunder restoration, as it has been damaged by vandals over the past few decades. Scientists have revealed that on the site of the present mausoleum there was an earlier structure, parts of which were used in the construction of the mausoleum. </item>

        <item>The eastern gate of the city of Osh in the form of a monumental one called Kyrgyz kochu is located at the entrance to the city from the south-eastern side along the Bishkek-Osh highway. When entering the city of Osh along Monuev Street, you can see a huge shining arch in the form of a Kyrgyz tunduk, which is provided with neon lighting at night.\n
The arch is 20 meters high. In front of the arch there is a statue of the great Kyrgyz Datka Alymbek, who majestically sits on a horse. On both sides, the statue of Alymbek Datka is guarded by two strong leopards.\n
The length of the monumental complex is 500 meters. High retaining walls were built on the side of the road reflecting the history of the Kyrgyz people and the Great Silk Road. All pictures are lined with natural river pebble mosaics.\n
In these pictures you can see the entire history and civilization of the Kyrgyz people. All this decoration can be seen only at night, as there are streetlights around the entire perimeter of the complex.\n
Note that the construction of the eastern gate was started in 2010, but was temporarily suspended due to the June events. In 2011, the grand opening of the monumental complex took place. </item>
        <item>One of the most impressive Lenin statues still standing in all of Central Asia appears to be objecting to the massive Kyrgyz flag flapping in front of him as he faces down the modern city hall.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>